The only way I've sold to people
is through emails.
Now, the biggest problem that people find,
especially fitness people, I hate to
have a go at you, I just know you well.
"Sign up to my emails
and I'll give you fitness tips." No,
thanks.
"I'll give you insights to fitness." No,
"I will help you be in the best shape of
your life." Cheers,
ChatGPT from Wish.
Give people something they want.
For golf. I don't play golf. "This
is my 19-stage formula that's going
to revolutionize the way
that you chip." Your title could even be,
"Stop
chipping wrong." Put your email address in
here, and over the next 19 days, we're
going to revolutionize how you see,
approach, and execute.
Is chips even a thing in golf?
I don't know.
You could be a swimming instructor.
"Your front crawl sucks.
Over the next 22 days,
we're going to be doing
real-life practical advice
and technique change that's going
to not only improve the speed in
which you swim, but make it
feel more effortless at the same time."
Wow!